A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor John G. Pollard, 1930-1934
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1930-1934., Extent: 2.45 cu. ft. (7 boxes). (Box Boxes 123-129)
  - Bland, S.O. (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Bradford, J.H. (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Burch, T.G. (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Byrd, Harry F. (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - C (Box 124, Folder 6-7)
  - California, Governor of (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Cannon, Bishop James (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Caperton, Mrs. (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Connecticut, Governor of (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Crab Story, 1930 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Crane, Richard (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - D (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Davis, Westmoreland (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Dudding, E.E. (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - E (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Eckener, Dr. Hugo (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Edison, T.A. (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Elections, Pollard (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Ethier, Bernard, Investigation, 1930 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - F (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Florida, Governor or (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Forney, Charles T. (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - G (Box 125, Folder 9-10)
  - Georgia, Governor of (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Glass, Carter (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - H (Box 126, Folder 1-2)
  - I (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Illinois, Governor of (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - J (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - K (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Kansas, Governor of (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Kentucky, Governor of (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - L (Box 127, Folder 1-2)
  - Louisiana, Governor of (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - M (Box 127, Folder 4-5)
  - Maryland, Governor of (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts, Governor of (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Mississippi, Governor of (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Missouri, Governor of (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Montague, A.J. (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - N (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - New Jersey, Governor of (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - New Mexico, Governor of (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - New York, Governor of (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Noell, Robert J. (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - North Carolina, Governor of (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - O (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - Ohio, Governor of (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - Oklahoma, Governor of (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Oregon, Governor of (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - P (Box 128, Folder 3-4)
  - Perry, George C. (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Pennsylvania, Governor of (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Q (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - R (Box 128, Folder 8-9)
  - Rhode Island, Governor of (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - Ruthven, Mary A. (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - S (Box 128, Folder 14-15)
  - S (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - South Carolina, Governor of (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Swanson, Claude A. (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - T (Box 129, Folder 4-5)
  - Tennessee, Governor of (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Texas, Governor of (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Tucker, Robert H. (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - U (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Utah, Governor of (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - V (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - W (Box 129, Folder 12-13)
  - West Virginia, Governor of (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Wisconsin, Governor of (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - X-Y (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Z (Box 129, Folder 17)
- Series III: Delegates Appointed, 1930-1934., Extent: 1.4 cu. ft. (4 boxes). (Box Boxes 130-133)
  The Delegates Appointed series, 1930-1934 is housed in four archival boxes and is arranged alphabetically by name of association or conference.
  - American Academy of Political and Social Science (Box 130, Folder 1-4)
  - American Forestry Association (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - American Legislators' Association (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - American Library Association (Box 130, Folder 7-10)
  - American Medical Association (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - American Mining Congress (Box 130, Folder 12-13)
  - American Prison Association (Box 130, Folder 14-17)
  - American Public Health Association (Box 130, Folder 18-19)
  - American Road Builders Association (Box 130, Folder 20-22)
  - American Shore and Beach Preservation Association (Box 130, Folder 23)
  - Atlantic Deeper Waterways (Box 130, Folder 24-27)
  - Eastern-Southern Conference on State Institutional Labor (Box 130, Folder 28)
  - Governor's Conference on Childhood and Youth (Box 130, Folder 29)
  - Institute of Public Affairs (Box 131, Folder 1-5)
  - International Recreation Congress (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - King's Mountain Battleground Celebration (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Meriwether Lewis Memorial Association (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 132, Folder 2-3)
  - National Association of State Auditors, Comptrollers, and Treasurers (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - National Conference on City Planning (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - National Conference of Social Work (Box 132, Folder 6-8)
  - National Conference on State Parks (Box 132, Folder 9-12)
  - National Conference on Street and Highway Safety (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - National Conference on Uniform Aeronautic Regulatory Laws (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - National Inter denominational Ministerial Alliance of America (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - National League of Compulsory Education Officials (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - National Recreation Congress (Box 132, Folder 17-18)
  - National Rivers and Harbors Congress (Box 133, Folder 1-3)
  - National Safety Congress (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - National Tax Association (Box 133, Folder 5-7)
  - Press Congress of the World (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Southeastern States Agricultural and Economic Conference (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Southern Forestry Congress (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - United States Good Roads Association (Box 133, Folder 11-14)
  - White House Conference on Child Health and Protection (Box 133, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Penal Affairs, 1930-1934., Extent: 8.4 cu. ft. (24 boxes). (Box Boxes 134-157)
  The Penal Affairs series, 1930-1934 is housed in twenty-four archival boxes and is arranged alphabetically by folder title. The series includes clemency files, renditions, requisitions, and pardons.
  - Clemency Extended, A-D, Index cards (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Clemency Extended, E-J, Index cards (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Clemency Extended, K-R, Index cards (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Clemency Extended, S-Z, Index cards (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Clemency Extended, Absolute Pardons, Commutation of Sentence, etc., Index cards (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Clemency Extended, Transfer to State Farm, Index cards (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Clemency Refused, A-D, Index cards (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Clemency Refused, E-I, Index cards (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Clemency Refused, J-N, Index cards (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Clemency Refused, O-R, Index cards (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Clemency Refused, S-Z, Index cards (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Requisitions, Index cards (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Requisitions, Made on, Alabama-Georgia, Index cards (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions, Made on, Illinois-New Jersey, Index cards (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Requisitions, Made on, New York-North Carolina, Index cards (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Requisitions, Made on, Ohio-South Carolina, Index cards (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions, Made on, Tennessee-West Virginia, Index cards (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, Miscellaneous (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, Trips not previously authorized (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, A (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, B (Box 138, Folder 4-5)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, B (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, C (Box 139, Folder 2-4)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, Canadian papers (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, D (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, Denton, E.L. (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, E (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, F (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, G (Box 141, Folder 1-2)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, Gerrior, Joseph H. (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, H (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, H (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, I (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, J (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, K (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, L (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, Mc (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, M (Box 143, Folder 2-3)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, Murray, J.G. (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, N (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, O (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, P (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, P (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, Peabody, Charles M. (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, Q (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, R (Box 144, Folder 4-5)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, S (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, S (Box 145, Folder 1-2)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, T (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, U (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, Upchurch, O.F. (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, V (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, W (Box 146, Folder 1-5)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, W (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, Wilson, W. (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, X (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, Y (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Requisitions, Requests for, Z (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Pardons, 1930-1933 (Box 147, Folder 6-8)
  - Pardons, Federal Prisons (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Pardons, Other states (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Pardons, Printed forms (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - Pardons, Requests, Letters from prisoners, 1930-1934 (Box 147, Folder 12-15)
  - Pardons, Requests, Letters from prisoners, 1930-1934 (Box 148, Folder 1-3)
  - Pardons, Restoration of Driving Privileges (Box 148, Folder 4-7)
  - Pardons, Suspension of Sentences (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Pardons, Abernathy - Brown, Daniel (Box 149)
  - Pardons, Brown, David - Culpeper (Box 150)
  - Pardons, Dalton - Hancock (Box 151)
  - Pardons, Hardy - Kitts (Box 152)
  - Pardons, Land - Murray (Box 153)
  - Pardons, Napier - Puckett (Box 154)
  - Pardons, Ramey - Sisk (Box 155)
  - Pardons, Skelton - Sykes (Box 156)
  - Pardons, Tarry - Young (Box 157)
- Series V: Financial Records, 1930-1934., Extent: 2.1 cu. ft. (6 boxes). (Box Boxes 158-163)
  The Financial Records are housed in six archival boxes and consist of monthly statements by the Comptroller, Annual Reports, Bonds, the Executive Control Fund and Miscellaneous.
  - Monthly Statements, As prepared by Comptroller, 1929 December (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Monthly Statements, As prepared by Comptroller, 1930 Jan-May (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Monthly Statements, As prepared by Comptroller, 1930 July-Sept. (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Monthly Statements, As prepared by Comptroller, 1930 Oct.-Dec. (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Monthly Statements, As prepared by Comptroller, 1931 Jan.-March (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Monthly Statements, As prepared by Comptroller, 1931 April-Aug. (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Monthly Statements, As prepared by Comptroller, 1931 Sept.-Dec. (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Monthly Statements, As prepared by Comptroller, 1932 Jan.-March (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Monthly Statements, As prepared by Comptroller, 1932 April-Aug. (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Monthly Statements, As prepared by Comptroller, 1932 Sept.-Dec. (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Monthly Statements, As prepared by Comptroller, 1933 Jan.-March (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Monthly Statements, As prepared by Comptroller, 1933 April-July (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Monthly Statements, As prepared by Comptroller, 1933 Aug.-Nov. (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Annual reports, Appropriation year ending 1930 Feb. 28 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Annual reports, Fiscal year ending 1932 June 30 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Bonds, Commonwealth Employees (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Bonds, Unemployment Relief Fund Agents, Cities (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Bonds, Unemployment Relief Fund Agents, Counties (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-01 (Box 161, Folder 1-5)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-01, Pay rolls (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-01, Purchase orders (Box 161, Folder 7-8)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-01, Vendor's invoice (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-02 (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-02 (Box 162, Folder 1-3)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-02, Pay rolls (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-01, Purchase orders (Box 162, Folder 5-7)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-01, Vendor's invoice (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-03 (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-05 (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-10 (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-50 (Box 162, Folder 12)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-51 (Box 162, Folder 13)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-52 (Box 162, Folder 14)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-53 (Box 162, Folder 15)
  - Executive Control Fund, 121-99-262 (Box 162, Folder 16)
  - Executive Control Fund, 124-50 (Box 162, Folder 17)
  - Executive Control Fund, Miscellaneous (Box 163, Folder 1-8)
- Series VI: Personal Records, 1930-1934., Extent: .35 cu. ft. (1 box). (Box Boxes 164)
  The Personal records consist of one box of transitional correspondence (November 1929-January 1930 and January 1934).
  - Transitional correspondence, 1929 Nov.-1930 Jan. (Box 164, Folder 1-22)
  - Governor Pollard's personal mail (Box 164, Folder 23)
  - Materials found in Governor Pollard's files after he left (Box 164, Folder 24)